[laughter]
Hello everybody.  So today we went for some
shopping.  I am coming from the road and mom has
eaten ice cream and my throat was sore
so I ate chocolate.  Nowadays a
new Magdi had opened in Hadwani.  So we thought let's
try something.  But what do I care, I am leaving
Hadwani soon.  Anyway,
after a mandatory pay cheque, we went
shopping for mom.  And
I got so bored sitting here that I said, "
Mom, please take me shopping too."  So
then I also looked at some suits for myself.
And after that we went to Nkaa to do some
shopping.  I wanted to
buy perfume for a long time but I could not find anything so
I did unnecessary shopping.
After seeing me and my mother shopping, Aarav also
hit the right spot and started telling us to make him do
shopping on the same note.  So
then I fulfilled his wish and
got him a football.  But he was not satisfied with this
and took us to the jersey shop.
Then finally mom took her bangles.
So this is how our shopping went.